[
  {
    "source":"mp3/2001SpaceOdyssey.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Interstellar",
    "choice2": "2001 A Space Odyssey",
    "choice3": "Star Trek",
    "choice4": "Gravity",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/BackToFuture.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Back To The Future",
    "choice2": "Independence Day",
    "choice3": "The Lord of the Rings",
    "choice4": "Neverending Story",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/TheExorcist.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Psycho",
    "choice2": "Halloween",
    "choice3": "The Exorcist",
    "choice4": "Poltergeist",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/ForestGump.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Superman",
    "choice2": "Harry Potter",
    "choice3": "X Men",
    "choice4": "Forest Gump",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/Halloween.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Halloween",
    "choice2": "The Village",
    "choice3": "The Shining",
    "choice4": "Blair Witch",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/CloseEncountersOfThirdKind.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "E.T",
    "choice2": "Close Encounters Of The Third Kind",
    "choice3": "Dances With Wolves",
    "choice4": "Good Will Hunting",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/HarryPotter.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Edward Scissorhands",
    "choice2": "Armageddon",
    "choice3": "Harry Potter",
    "choice4": "Last Of The Mohicans",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/Platoon.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Under Siege",
    "choice2": "Robocop",
    "choice3": "Rambo",
    "choice4": "Platoon",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/IndianaJones.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Indiana Jones",
    "choice2": "Willow",
    "choice3": "Star Trek",
    "choice4": "Jurassic Park",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/TheGreatEscape.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "The Bridge on the River Kwai",
    "choice2": "The Great Escape",
    "choice3": "Guns Of Navarone",
    "choice4": "The Dirty Dozen",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/Up.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Finding Nemo",
    "choice2": "WALL-E",
    "choice3": "Up",
    "choice4": "Cars",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/PulpFiction.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Reservoir Dogs",
    "choice2": "Natural Born Killers",
    "choice3": "Kill Bill",
    "choice4": "Pulp Fiction",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/StarWars.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "The Hobbit",
    "choice2": "Star Wars",
    "choice3": "Dune",
    "choice4": "Avatar",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/WallaceAndGromit.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Chicken Run",
    "choice2": "Creature Comforts",
    "choice3": "Wallace & Gromit",
    "choice4": "Shaun the Sheep",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"mp3/Superman.mp3",
    "question":"This is the the them song of which movie?",
    "choice1": "Batman",
    "choice2": "Iron Man",
    "choice3": "Spider-Man",
    "choice4": "Superman",
    "answer": 4
  }
]